jobsfone.com 2011-11-18

# JobsFone.com

JobsFone.com Online Privacy Policy

This Online Privacy Policy covers the operations of the (www.JobsFone.com) website that you are visiting. 

**Role of the Website** ****  
The purpose of this website is to describe the JobsFone.com services – Job Alerts , Job content , Employer Solutions , Candidate Solutions 

    **Anonymity for Casual Visitors**   
Our website does not use any analytical tools to capture personally identifiable information from visitors to the site. Casual visitors - just seeking information about services  \- are given anonymity. However, we use analytic tools (including cookies) to capture marketing and aggregate visitor information about how people use our site and how they may have been directed to our site by marketing partners and agents. If cookies cannot be set, we may use IP addresses to identify the web browser. Many browsers may share an IP address, such as a proxy server, which prohibits these addresses from unique identification.  
**What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**   
The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  1. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  2. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  3. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

**We Don’t Sell or Give Information for Outside Marketing**   
All personally identifiable information we obtain from visitors is used exclusively by our staff, to fulfill the requests made by visitors, or for visitor-accepted continuing communications by our staff. We never sell or give visitor personal information to any third party for marketing uses. 

**Privacy Policy Changes - Future Development**   
As we grows, we expect to add features to this web site. When we do that, we will continue to follow the Online Privacy Policies described here. Should changes in our Online Privacy Policy be needed to cover such new features, we will indicate such changes in the Online Policy.
